[theme music playing]
-You have to throw up!
-Guys, guys, I'm just joking.
I didn't put poison in this.
I'd rather get married than mourn.
Don't overshadow my moment.
And I did tell you, Emilia. Don't try me.
-[grunts]
-Emilia!
Oh, Emilia. Help!
-I love you! I love you!
-Reporting for duty, Mayor.
-Madrigal.
-Just like old times, Mayor.
The only difference is that
I work for Jaguar now.
[gunshots]
What was that?! Secure Arnaldo, hurry!
Emilia? Emilia?
Don't worry, Emilia.
You'll regain your strength. Believe me.
[Emilia] Why don't you want to
show your face to me?
[Raul] Because your opinion of
me might change.
[Arnaldo] If he thinks Jaguar
can protect him, he's wrong.
-Madrigal works for Jaguar?
-Yes.
What's that? Why are you wounded?!
Anna, this is nothing.
What if you get caught next time?
Or worse, they kill you?
I won't let them catch me alive!
I'd rather shoot myself in the head, Anna!
I'll do anything to stop them
from getting married.
[Ivy] The Jepoy that I knew
would never join forces
with that monster Jaguar.
Fine, Ivy. I've changed.
I let my emotions control my decisions.
But I did everything for you.
I let my feelings get the best of me
because I love you, not just as a friend!
I love you, Ivy.
[Emilia] I must admit, I enjoy
the feeling of being bad.
I didn't know you were a great lover.
That's why I've made my decision.
We'll take my father down together.
You'll make my dream come true.
You and I will be the king
and queen of this province.
-Was I wrong to love Ivy?
-It's never wrong to love.
It's just that sometimes
some things aren't meant to be.
It's not like they can't understand.
They're just scared something
bad might happen to you.
Diego, I know how deeply
concerned you are.
But this is a risk I have to take.
Hon.
Grandpa and I decided that from
tonight until the wedding day,
you'll just stay here.
You aren't going out.
It's like you've imprisoned me.
That's exactly what it is.
It should be like this,
so no one can steal you from me.
This wedding must and will happen.
Ivy!
I'm so glad I can finally visit
the imprisoned bride.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am sure. I promise.
The reason I came here is to apologize.
I'm sorry for what I did
during the bridal shower.
I realized I shouldn't go against you.
Really, Emilia?
Yes. I sincerely mean it.
[sighs] I want the
wedding to push through,
so I can finally
welcome you to the family.
Sometimes, you're mean,
but you're sweet most of the time.
Of course.
And since you want to
welcome me to your family,
can I call you Mom from now on?
Yes! Sure. [chuckles]
Daughter-in-law?
[chuckles]
[Emilia] Um…
So, anyway, just relax here
in your little prison.
But I'm sure you won't die or anything.
Bye.
You too, Mom.
Relax and be careful
with what you eat and drink.
What with the poison and all.
But I'm sure you won't die.
[tense music playing]
Not just yet.
Your grave still needs to be dug.
Just you wait, Mom.
It'll be worth it.
I want the perimeter of the
wedding venue tightly secured.
If needed, let's place snipers
in strategic areas.
Deploy your private army too.
I want a lot of men standing by.
And place barbed wire to be safe.
Understood, Mayor.
Understood, Congressman.
And while we're at it, bring fire trucks.
Just in case we need to disperse people.
Because our intel
suggests people
will be protesting in the plaza.
[Julio scoffs]
The nerve of those people.
Anyway, I don't want
your security people to be lax.
I want you to punish the protesters
if they get in your way.
Disperse them harshly.
If anyone starts trouble, shoot them down,
so they'll know that I mean business.
Sit and have some rest.
We still have a long way.
Food is on its way.
Okay? And water.
-Use your time to rest.
-All right.
-We have a long day ahead.
-This guy's gonna like eating.
[Marlon] Danny, don't let them
touch the floor.
[Fernan] Look at it, it's dirty.
This is dirty.
What's the deal?
Batch? What's wrong?
The wedding's tomorrow.
Are you ready?
I'm not thinking about myself anymore.
Batch, we need to be alert.
Something big will happen tomorrow.
What do you mean? What's going to happen?
You'll know.
We just have to be ready.
Come on, let's go back to the campaign.
You sure you're okay?
All right.
So, you guys doing okay?
[tense music playing]
It's all right.
You can imprison me in here,
but you can't stop my plans.
[phone ringing]
Mom?
Lily.
Lily, I want to see you…
I want to be with you before your wedding.
Please?
Can I see you today?
Okay, Mom. I'll be there.
Thank you, Lily.
[music slowly fades]
Tomorrow, you're going to be
Mrs. Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
Mm-hmm.
And I can't wait, hon.
Me neither.
I really can't wait.
Just one more--
Mmm.
-Come on!
-Arnaldo!
Come on, Ivy.
If I had my way, I would like to
spend the night here with you.
Please, let me.
Hon. I want that too.
But I'm holding back because
I'm scared of the saying.
The bride and groom can't be
together before they get married
because the wedding
might not push through.
Do you want that?
We're going to have bad luck.
The wedding won't happen.
Of course, you don't. I know I don't.
So?
Okay.
I'm just scared that when I wake up…
you'll be gone.
You've left and gone far away.
No, hon.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not leaving you.
Tomorrow, I'll be at our wedding.
I'll be there in the church, hon.
I promise.
I'll be there.
Okay.
I'll take your word for it.
Hmm. Go on.
It's getting really difficult
to control myself, Arnaldo.
Tomorrow, I'm yours.
[suspenseful music]
-Tomorrow?
-Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Rest.
Mrs. Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
I like the sound of that.
-Good night, hon.
-Good night.
Don't I get a goodnight kiss?
Here.
See? You're making this hard for me.
It's just here.
Okay, bye.
-Hon, bye.
-See?
I'm having a hard time when you do that.
-One more day.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
One more day.
I'll see you tomorrow.
One more day, one more day, one more day…
[ominous music playing]
Be ready tomorrow, Arnaldo.
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh, Lily. Why aren't you here yet?
[heavy breathing]
Mom.
Lily, dear!
[instrumental theme music playing]
I thought I'd never get
to see you before your wedding.
Lily, I'm scared.
Lily, I can't imagine you
getting married to our enemy.
What if they keep you away from me?
What if this is the last time
that I'll get to hold you?
Mom, that's not going to happen.
I already told you that the Ardientes
will never keep us apart.
Never again.
Mom, just have faith in me.
Trust me, Mom.
I'm sorry, Mom.
[instrumental theme music
continues playing]
Miss Prianka…
Thank you.
Thank you so much for what you did.
Thank you for everything you've taught me.
Ivy Aguas wouldn't exist…
if it weren't for you.
I wouldn't be able to attain
justice if it weren't for you.
Thank you, Miss Prianka.
Dad…
Dad, we were so happy then.
Our family used to be happy…
until the Ardientes destroyed it.
Dad, do you remember my promise…
to get justice?
It's within my reach, Dad.
And I promise you, Dad…
that after I succeed,
Mom and I will be all right.
[somber music playing]
But my family will never be
complete without you here, Dad.
This is for you, Dad.
This is for our family.
I was the lucky one, Nanny.
I was so lucky you were there.
Because you gave me all your love.
You loved me with all your heart,
that's why I'm so fortunate.
And that's why it still hurts.
It hurts so much.
And I hate myself
for dragging you into this mess.
You were a victim
in my search for revenge!
Nanny.
Nanny, please forgive me.
I'm sorry for getting you involved
in my search for revenge!
[sobbing]
I promise you,
I will make that bastard feel…
just how tight a rope
around the neck can be.
He'll pay with his life.
I love you all so much.
[dramatic music playing]
[sobbing]
[breathing deeply]
[tense music playing]
Everything will be over soon.
[Dante] Once we settle down
in Poblacion Ardiente,
we'll have enough money to spare.
And it won't be long
until I build my own private law firm.
[young Lily] Wow!
[Dante] This is going to be our new home!
[young Lily] 365 Days?
[Dante] For an entire year full of love!
We'll have the peaceful life
you've been dreaming of.
[crying]
How dare you?!
-You killed my husband!
-Mom, calm down.
You murderers!
-What happened to you?
-[shushes]
[Tonio] Hey!
Lily… Run!
Soon, this town will finally be free…
from the Ardiente family's grip.
Hurry! Hurry! Here!
Look over there.
Here!
-What--
-Why? Here!
[indistinct chatter]
-Step aside.
-Make way!
[indistinct chatter]
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey, Grandpa.
Arnaldo.
[chuckles]
Look at you!
Dressed to the nines!
What sartorial elegance.
[chuckles] Thank you.
I have a special gift for you.
Wow!
Thank you, Grandpa!
It seemed like the right gift.
Very symbolic.
My time is ending
and yours is just about to start.
[chuckling]
I can't even believe
that you're getting married.
Going back in time…
I remember you as that bratty, little boy.
Now, you've grown up
to be a fine gentleman.
You've come a long way, Arnaldo.
[soft music playing]
I'm so blessed
to have a grandson like you.
I've been given a second chance
to feel like a father again.
Because of your obedience
and your respect for me.
You are the son…
that I never had.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm so proud of you, Arnaldo.
Thank you, Grandpa.
I won't let you down.
I know you won't. I know.
[Emilia] Arnaldo.
[chuckles]
Look at you!
-You look so good!
-Thank you.
-You look so great.
Looks like you're ready, but…
I'm not ready to let you go.
You understand why I'm like this, right?
I mean, all mothers are like this.
They want to protect their kids
from getting hurt.
And, I'm sorry that I doubted you.
I should've trusted you.
I should've remembered
you were also an Ardiente,
and Ardientes are strong, resilient,
and, most of all, cunning.
[pensive music playing]
I should've never doubted you.
-It's okay, Mom.
-I love you, son.
I love you too. I love you too.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'd already forgiven you. You and Dad.
Thank you, son.
And I figured we should let this wedding
be a fresh start for all of us.
And I'm looking forward to it.
[Arnaldo] How does that sound?
-Sounds fine to me.
-[Emilia and Raul chuckling]
Sounds very fine.
Let's give the groom a big hug.
Viva Ardiente.
[all] Viva Ardiente.
[dramatic music playing]
Don't worry, Auntie.
They'll definitely save Lily.
[dramatic music swelling]
Here's the package you've been
waiting for, Miss Aguas.
And the Mayor and his family already left.
[suspenseful music playing]
We are now reporting live
at Poblacion Ardiente
to witness the royal wedding
of Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo
and Miss Ivy Aguas.
Friends, citizens, please have a seat.
The wedding's about to start.
[no audible dialogue]
People are quickly
gathering outside the venue.
The police and the military
are also in full force
to ensure everyone's safety.
The cameras are in place
for the live coverage,
which you can watch right here…
-Aisen! Aisen!
-on the Ardiente TV Network…
-What?
-Look.
…at Poblacion Ardiente.
So stay tuned!
The royal wedding is about to start!
[kids] Yay!
It's the Ardiente's royal wedding.
-Oh, yeah!
-It's starting!
[cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
[dreamy music playing]
-Good afternoon, Madame.
-Good day.
[mouthing] Wow! It's beautiful!
[dreamy music continues]
Shall we?
Hello, friends.
[foreboding music playing]
[foreboding music continues]
I'm in position.
I'll make sure no one
gets in your way, Ivy.
Not even the Ardientes themselves.
[tense music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
Relax, Arnaldo.
Nothing can stop your wedding.
Ivy's late, Grandpa.
What if…
What if she doesn't show up?
[chuckles]
Calm down, my son. Calm down.
She'll be here.
[tense music playing]
Jepoy.
What are you doing here?
You know why I'm here.
I'm gonna stop the wedding.
And I'll stop whoever gets in my way.
Even you, Diego.
[Jepoy] I warned you.
[gun cocks]
Jepoy, this isn't the right
time for you to interfere.
What do we do? Nothing?
-We let them get married?
-Ivy has plans.
What do you know about Ivy's plans?
Everything.
[suspenseful music playing]
Excuse me, Papa.
I'll just make a phone call.
Don't take too long.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
Are you in position?
Yes, ma'am. I'm in position.
Ready to fire once the bride arrives.
Okay.
[grunting]
Make sure that Ivy Aguas
doesn't enter the church alive.
Is that clear?
Your assassin's unconscious, Emilia.
[tense music playing]
Diego?
Diego…
If you think I hired only one hitman,
then you're mistaken.
If Ivy Aguas happens
to enter the church alive,
what makes you think
she'll get out alive too?
What is it?
You're going to have Ivy killed.
Please, Raul, stay out of this.
Stay out of this?
If your father finds out
about this, he'll be furious.
He wants this wedding to happen.
No! Ivy Aguas has to die.
Raul, she's going to replace me
in this family.
Do you understand?
If you destroy Arnaldo's life…
He'll get over this heartache,
just like everybody does.
And who's going to help him
if not his own mother?
Remember, Raul…
I got over the most painful
heartache in my life.
And that's by getting over you.
Is that it? You're over me? Are you sure?
Enough, Raul. I don't have time for this.
I have a bride to kill,
so if you'll excuse me.
-There are other hitmen?
-Yeah.
-How many?
-I don't know.
Jepoy.
Go inside, I'll handle this.
Go on. I'll follow.
Okay.
[woman] Ladies and gentlemen,
the bride is arriving.
So, may I please ask everyone
to please go inside first,
so we can start the ceremony?
Let's go inside first, ma'am.
Let's go inside, ma'am, okay?
[cheers]
Ivy! Ivy!
[woman] Thank you. Let's get
inside, so we can begin.
I need you to get inside.
Everyone, please…
[indistinct chatter]
Your wife-to-be is here, okay?
Okay. Best man?
Please stay here.
-Oh, yes.
-Fall in line.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Okay, thank you.
-Miss Claire.
[dramatic music playing]
[orchestra playing]
[music slowly fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[eerie music playing]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues playing]
Yes, I'm wearing black.
Because this is the only color
that suits this occasion.
["Wildflower" instrumental playing]
["Wildflower" instrumental continues]
Did I surprise you?
You were never one for tradition.
Shall we?
Papa, look how Ivy Aguas
is disrespecting us.
I can't let her do this to the family.
I don't give a hoot
if she came here in black, pink, red,
or wearing nothing
but that necklace on her neck.
What matters to me is that she came
and that she will marry Arnaldo.
And, in a little while,
she will be an Ardiente.
Now, if she's got something bad planned,
she will suffer like
everyone else who does us wrong.
[tense music playing]
Come to think of it,
that black gown suits her, Papa.
You're right, Raul. It does suit her.
It's perfect for what
will happen to her later.
[priest] If anyone knows of any reason why
Ivy and Arnaldo should not be married,
speak now or forever hold your peace.
[Jepoy] What's that?
-You're one of Emilia's hitmen.
-No--
[grunting]
[priest] Do you, Arnaldo,
take Ivy to be your lawfully wedded wife?
I do. I do.
[bomb ticking]
[priest] Do you, Ivy,
take Arnaldo to be
your lawfully wedded husband?
[suspenseful music playing]
[mouthing] Ivy…
[sobbing]
[theme music playing]